http://www.ceoexpress.com/html/privacy.aspx

Login
LOGIN
Username:
Password:
Remember Login
Login Problems?
Forgot Your Password?
CEOExpress Company LLC Privacy Policy
CEOExpress Company LLC takes your privacy seriously. CEOExpress will never sell, rent or in any other way make your personal information available to a third party.
We collect information from our members during the registration process. This information is used to develop relationships with our members and to continually enhance the CEOExpress Web site. We hold our users and your privacy concerns in the highest regard. Maintaining your privacy is critical to us. Please take a moment to read our Privacy Policy for a better understanding of the measures we take to protect you.
We may make content or services from other Web sites, including our affiliated or co-branded ones, available to you from links located on CEOExpress. These other Web sites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you review each individual Web site's Privacy Policy when asked for personal information when visiting them. While we attempt to carefully screen our partners, CEOExpress assumes no responsibility for the Privacy Policies on any of the sites outside of its direct control.
Cookies: By using CEOExpress, you agree to the use of cookies. For use of the public page, cookies are not linked to any personally identifiable information, but allow some personalization of this page without having to sign in to a member account. For use of the member version of CEOExpress, cookies allow you to view your personal page and remain logged in to your account.
Advertising: Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their privacy policy or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com. Exponential cookie information is:
Cookie Name
Domain
Function
Party
Class
Type
Expiry
ANON_ID
tribalfusion.com
The anonymous hashed Id in the cookie links the web user's browser to a profile which contains the behavior the user has displayed
Third
Tracking
Persistent
3 months
CEOExpress Privacy Policy:
How we use the information we collect
How is the information collected?
Managing your user profile
CEOExpress rights and responsibilities
Subpoena compliance information
1. How We Use the Information We Collect
To customize the content you see on your pages.
For your convenience, your forms are pre-populated to save you time.
For aggregate, statistical information on the audience so that we can continually refine and improve our product offerings.
Occasionally, we will communicate via email regarding new features and services that you may be interested in. You may "opt out" of these announcements at any time, though we may still use the email address you provide in order to respond to inquiries, or provide important information.
2. How is the Information Collected?
Registration: During the registration process we ask you to supply personal information such as your name, email address and title as well as general information such as your industry, company size, zip or postal code, state or province, and country. CEOExpress Company LLC collects this information to know our users better, with the goal of providing you with the best possible services.
Our E-commerce partner, Authorizenet.com, the world's leading payment authorization service for online business, is responsible for handling your payment authorization. They collect your financial data including contact name, credit card information and demographic information on their secure site. This information is strictly confidential and their Privacy Statement is available online. CEOExpress does not retain copies of this information on its own servers.
Web Site Usage Information: We automatically collect IP addresses and Web site usage information when you visit our Web site. This information helps us evaluate how our subscribers use and navigate our Web sites on an aggregate basis, including the number and frequency of visitors to each Web page, and the length of their visits. We do not monitor usage on an individual basis.
Surveys: We may conduct occasional online surveys to improve our service our seek the opinions of our users. These surveys are entirely voluntary and you may easily decline to participate.
Tell A Friend: You may choose to recommend the CEOExpress Web site to a friend. Once you provide their name and email address we will send them a one-time mailing inviting them to visit CEOExpress. The name and address information is used for this one purpose only and will not be permanently stored.
Cookies: A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive that is necessary to identify and dynamically build your customized page. This cookie is not linked to any personally identifiable information, but it allows you to have your personalized page without having to sign in. You may eliminate the cookie at any time by "signing out" of your personal page. This option is prominently displayed on the CEOExpress homepage.
Children: The CEOExpress Web site is not directed at individuals under thirteen years of age (or older based on your country), and CEOExpress does not intend to collect any personally-identifiable information from such individuals.
3. Managing Your User Profile
You have the ability to modify your personal information that you have shared with CEOExpress under "My Account," a link prominently displayed on the homepage. All fields of your personal information are viewable. Everything except your User Name, which is needed to create your customized pages, can be modified. At any point after registration you can modify your demographic data, email address, password and more. You also have the opportunity to choose whether or not to be on our mailing list. If you sign up for an email and/or stock portfolio account, you will always have the option to delete these. Instructions for deletion are detailed in the Help sections of each of these programs.
We do continue to store your information, and do not delete your account customization after your cancel your account. This allows members to come back later and access their existing account. If you wish to have all of your information and customization removed from our database at any time, just contact us at webmaster@ceoexpressmail.com.
How to Opt-Out: You must provide registration information if you wish to use select features on CEOExpress, however, you may choose to "opt out" of receiving promotional materials from CEOExpress at any time. When you receive an email communication from us you will be able to opt-out of future communications. You may also opt out of receiving any communication from us by contacting us at webmaster@ceoexpressmail.com.
4. CEOX Social Privacy
About CEOX SocialCEOX Social is a social media management tool, which helps you quickly and easily post to social media accounts like LinkedIn, Facebook, and Twitter, all from one place, and is a feature of CEOExpress.com.
You must register for either a CEOX Social-only upgraded free CEOExpress account, or a full featured CEOExpressSelect membership in order to use this service. When registering for either CEOExpress account, you provide personal information to CEOExpress. In order to use the CEOX Social service, you must connect to your LinkedIn, Facebook, and/or Twitter accounts, as well.
Third-PartiesThis Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of any third-party services such as LinkedIn, Facebook or Twitter, that you elect to access through the CEOX Social service, or to any applications developed by third parties that CEOExpress does not own or control. The Privacy Policy does not cover information you provide to Third-Party Services accessed via CEOX Social. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third-Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of any Third-Party Services. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third-Party Services you access via CEOX Social.
Personal InformationDuring registration and use of CEOX Social through a CEOExpress account we may collect some personal information about you, such as:
your full name and email address
the user name and password you choose for CEOExpress login
your zip code
other optional information as part of your account profile
information you submit in the form of posts published to social media services, via CEOX Social
images that you may publish via CEOX Social
information we may receive relating to communications you send us, such as queries or comments concerning our services
CEOExpress uses the collected information for the following general purposes:
to identify you when you log in to your account
to enable us to provide services to you
to contact you about your account and provide support
to keep you informed of information about our services we think you may find useful or which you have requested from us, provided you have indicated you would like to be contacted for these purposes
By submitting information to CEOExpress when registering, you consent to the use of your information for these purposes.
In order to use CEOX Social, you may connect to LinkedIn, Facebook, or Twitter. When you connect a Third-Party Service to your CEOExpress CEOX Social account, we may access other information related to your social profiles. When that occurs, a prompt will inform you of the details that will be accessible by CEOExpress. These may include information such as:
your LinkedIn, Facebook, or Twitter user name
your first and last name or company/organization name associated with your LinkedIn, Facebook, or Twitter account
publishing permissions, to allow you to publish statuses to your own timelines and pages
publishing permissions, to allow you to publish photos to your own timelines and pages
CEOExpress will never publish anything to your LinkedIn, Facebook, or Twitter accounts that you did not write and schedule for publishing through your CEOX Social account.
5. CEOExpress Rights and Responsibilities
Security: The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personal information. In case of a security breach, CEOExpress members will be notified within 72 hours.
Policy Modifications: CEOExpress may edit this policy from time to time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that these changes will not use the personal information you submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy without your prior consent.
Banner Ads: CEOExpress Company LLC has a written agreement with our advertising agent, the company that serves our banner ads, that it will not collect any personally identifiable information from the users of CEOExpress.
Rights: CEOExpress reserves the right to disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our Subscriber Agreement or Terms and Conditions of Use. We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so.
6. Subpoena compliance information
If you seek the identity or account information of a CEOExpress account user in connection with a civil legal matter, you must fax, mail, or serve CEOExpress with a valid subpoena.
Submission of Subpoenas: CEOExpress Company LLC is located in Boston MA, and all civil subpoenas should be served at that location or mailed or faxed to:
CEOExpress Company LLC
Attn: Client Services
1 Boston Place
Suite 2600
Boston, MA 02108
fax: 617-299-8649
Fees for Subpoena Compliance: CEOExpress Company LLC will charge the person or entity submitting the civil subpoena for costs associated with subpoena compliance. Payment must be made within thirty (30) days from the date of receipt of the CEOExpress invoice. Checks should be made out to CEOExpress Company LLC
CEOExpress Company LLC subpoena compliance costs are as follows:
If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please complete a Feedback Form.
This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 23, 2018.
617 482 1200617 299 8649 (fax)
Contact
As an Amazon AssociateCEOExpress earns fromqualifying purchases.
©1999-2020 CEOExpress Company LLC
Copyright & Disclaimer  |  Privacy Policy  |  Terms & Conditions
